As you work through the course, you'll
be required to download a range of files.
Some of these relate to practice
tasks within each of the sessions.
But the most important files are the ones
that you need to complete the assessment.
Now I've downloaded these already and I've
placed them in a folder and they're just
in my documents folder on the computer.
And as you can see I have - there are
seven files - they're all in one folder.
However, as I work through the course, I'm
going to download further files, whether
they be practice files or assessment
files for presentations and spreadsheets.
So one of the good things to get
into the habit of doing is saving
files into specific folders.
This allows you to find your files
quite quickly and be organised.
So to arrange them into a
folder, the first thing I need
to do is to create a folder.
So there are two ways of doing that.
If I'm on the home tab and just
click on the new folder icon there.
There's an, also an icon on
the quick access task bar.
And another way of doing it is, as you
can see, when I hover over it is Control
Shift and N which is just a shortcut, but
I'm just going to click on the new folder,
which will then create a new folder.
Now, as all the files that I
have downloaded relate to the
WP2 assessment, I'm going to
call the folder WP2 assessment.
And just click away from that.
And then that has created the folder.
So now I can quite simply move each of
the files into the WP2 assessment folder.
Once I have all of those in there, I just
click on the folder and you can see all
of the files are now included in there.
So that's a WP2 assessment.
Now, as I work through the course, I'm
going to download further files for
PS2 and spreadsheets and some files at
relate to the improving productivity.
So what I would need to do is I need
to create folders for each of them.
So I create a new folder and
I'll call that PS2 assessment.
And then another folder
called SS2 assessment.
So again, I've got three folders
for the three programs that I
will be using, but in addition to
that, I may want to organise those
folders within an overall folder.
So what I will do, I want to create a
new folder and call that one ITQ level
two, and then I'm going to move those
folders into the ITQ level two folder.
And again, that just keeps all
of the information organised.
So I have PS2 assessment, SS2
assessment, WP2 assessment.
For the practice files that I download, I
would probably create a new, another new
folder and call that WP2 practice files.
And again, as I move forward, when
I download the files for the PS2
practice and the SS2 practice,
I will create more folders.
As you can see, this just allows
you to organise your files into
specific folders which ensures that
you can access them quite quickly.
And you know where everything is stored.